<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dimeiza&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://Dimeiza.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dimeiza&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 02:45:02 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://Dimeiza.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a &#34;Remote work environment by lying down&#34; with Oculus Quest</title>
      <link>https://Dimeiza.github.io/2020/remoteworkwithoculusquest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 02:45:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Dimeiza.github.io/2020/remoteworkwithoculusquest/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The force of COVID-19 is extremely powerful, even in the company that was reluctant to remote work, movement of remote work is emrerging.
So, I have worked from my home, and I hoped to contribute reserving of social distance for company and society.
And recently, I have suffered from back pain.
I have a Aeron chair and usually used it.
https://store.hermanmiller.com/office/office-chairs/aeron-chair/2195348.html?lang=en_US#lang=en_US&amp;amp;hpn=1&amp;amp;start=1
But in this time, famous and excellent chair can&amp;rsquo;t helped me to sit a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a handmade fanless NAS with NanoPi M4 and SATA Hat</title>
      <link>https://Dimeiza.github.io/2019/makingnaswithnanopim4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 08:16:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Dimeiza.github.io/2019/makingnaswithnanopim4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When I rearranged my room, I suddenly wanted to replace my old NAS.
I have used this.
 It was so useful NAS, But It was a bit large.
So I had tried to replace NAS with NUC, but it wasn’t stable because my NUC had a problem in its power unit.
Then I heard cases that build NAS with Linux single board, so I thought to try it with hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini-ITX PC with GPU powerd by In Win Chopin(no customized case)</title>
      <link>https://Dimeiza.github.io/2019/chopinwithgpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 08:16:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Dimeiza.github.io/2019/chopinwithgpu/</guid>
      <description>Today I introduce a bit of pc customize technique with famous mini-ITX case.
I decided to publish this method because I seem this know-how isn’t popular.
Introduction I have a famous mini-ITX case made by In Win. Chopin.
 This is my favolite case.
But my main PC(Ryzen 7 1800X) has been built with DAN cases A4-SFX(It also be awesome case!). Therefore Chopin was used for building a 2nd PC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
